Black Cadillacs is a drama film directed by Marlida Ferreira.
The story of two friends on leave after serving in Afghanistan.
Together they make the trip home for thanksgiving
where friends and family await.
They reminisce and question if one can ever really go back home.
Rua, played by Shannon Barnett.
Tighe, played by Sean Clement.
Siobhan, played by Rachel Gassi.
Finn, played by PJ Lazic.
Catherine, played by Tamsen McDonough.
Alana, played by Patricia McKenzie.
"Two Black Cadillacs" is a song by American recording artist Carrie
Underwood, taken from her fourth studio album, Blown Away.
The song served as the album's third single on
November 18, 2012, through Arista Nashville.
Written by Underwood, Hillary Lindsey, and Josh Kear, "Two Black Cadillacs" features lyrics addressing the story
of two women who, when they realize they are both involved with the same man, decide to kill him.
It was produced by Mark Bright, and the instrumentation was
compared to songs by Dixie Chicks and Miranda Lambert.
Upon its release, "Two Black Cadillacs" was met with positive reviews from music
critics, who praised its story and Underwood's versatility as an artist.
Commercially, the song was successful.
In the United States, it reached number two on the Billboard Country
Airplay chart, and also reached number 41 on the Hot 100.
As of July 2020, "Two Black Cadillacs" was certified 2× Platinum by
the Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA).
The song also charted in Canada at number three on the Country
chart and at number 52 on the Canadian Hot 100.
The accompanying music video was directed by P.R.
Brown, and filmed in Nashville, Tennessee.
The video draws inspiration from Stephen King's novel Christine, and shows how the
wife and mistress kill the cheating husband with a black Cadillac.
It was nominated for Video of the Year at the 2013
Academy of Country Music Awards.
Underwood has performed "Two Black Cadillacs" in a number of live appearances, including at the 55th Annual Grammy Awards, where various images were
projected onto the singer's gown, and at the 2013 Country Music Association Awards, in a medley with "Good Girl", "See You Again", and "Blown Away".
It was also performed during the Blown Away Tour.
The tone is emotional.